[Music] It's been
15 years since I became a Maths teacher at PS School. I
live my life with pride and responsibility. I
think about the future of my students day and night.
But I often think about my own future too.
When I become Hemant Thakkar, a teacher,
and make rules only for myself.
I will still need income.
That's why I need a reliable plan
that provides guaranteed income even after retirement,
so that I can still live a good life with pride and responsibility. We will
support you in fulfilling all your responsibilities. Don't be fooled. ICICI
Prudential Life brings you a
new-age plan, ICICI Prudential Sukh
Samriddhi, which will provide you with a regular
guaranteed income so that you can fulfill your dreams, big or small.
If,
like Hemant Thakkar, you are looking for a guaranteed income for your retirement, the
ICICI
Prudential Sukh Samriddhi income option
offers you many benefits. If you
pay a premium of Rs 50,000 every year for 10 years, then
after the premium payment term is over,
you will get Rs 51 every year.  You will get a guaranteed income of ₹563
for the next 8 years. Apart from this,
you will also be given a lump sum amount on the maturity of the policy.
You can use the due date feature
which will give you income on the date of your choice. The
savings wallet feature of this policy
gives you the choice that if you do not need income in any year, you
can deposit that income with us in the savings wallet. This
deposited amount will keep growing and
you can withdraw it anytime. You
can use this feature whenever you want during the policy term
and you are also protected by life cover for the entire policy term. So,
like Hemant Thakkar,
fulfill all your needs with the happiness and prosperity of ICICI. Listen to
ICICI Prudential Life Insurance,
your trusted partner in fulfilling every dream of you and your loved ones.
[Music]